# CAO TRONG TÍN

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

**4.** 0949684530 ■ tin.caotrong@gmail.com **4.** https://www.linkedin.com/in/caotrongtin99/

#### **OBJECTIVE**

I have about 2+ years of experience building modern web applications. My strengths are having a strong, deep base of knowledge and quickly getting used to technologies (i have experienced a lot of tech-stacks), deeply caring for the product, and always trying to improve myself to deliver better and better output.

### TECHNICAL SKILLS

**Programing Language** Javascript/Typescript

Frontend ReactJS, Next.js, Redux, Redux Thunk

Backend Node.js, Express.js, NestJS, Sequelize, GraphQL, Socket.io, Docker, ElasticSearch,

RabbitMO

PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Redis Database Mocha, Chai, Jest, Cypress **Testing** 

Knowledge Basic knowledge in Microservice, CI/CD, Ubuntu

## WORK EXPERIENCE

TMA Solutions - Front-end Developer (ReactJS) Intern

Sep 2019 - Jan 2020

- Participate in company internal projects.
- Research and learn new technologies.

# SaveMoney Corporation - Fullstack Web Developer

May 2020 - May 2021

- Coordinating with other teams in the same project.
- Participate in Agile software development.
- Develop Front-end & Backend and maintain Nodejs-based web application.
- Participate in the process of understanding and analyzing requirements and optimizing systems.
- Working with great partners such as ZapoPay, VNPay, PVI,...

#### Spirit Labs - Fullstack Web Developer

May 2021 - Now

- Develop products for Singapore clients.
- Develop Front-end application using Next.js and Backend application using Node.js.

# Bloom Asia - Fullstack Web Developer

November 2021 - Now

- Develop products for Austrailia clients.
- Responsible for web development using Nodejs, Reactis

## **EDUCATION**

HCMC University of Science - Major: Software Engineering

July 2017 - Aug 2021

GPA: 3.38/4.00

## **PROJECTS**

The Dolce Diet (March 2022 - Now)

Customer	Mike Dolce
Description	Mike Dolce is an award winning MMA trainer leading the market in weight loss and living a healthy lifestyle. His web-platform is the gateway for consumers to become a part of his program which incorporates not only the meal and exercise plans but also a key piece of technology incorporated from a Bloom Partner organization which provides constant analysis of data inputs to allow for the most up-to-date assessment of progress.
Team size	6
My position	Fullstack Web Developer
My responsibilities	<ul> <li>Migrate application from PHP, Angular to Nodejs, Reactjs</li> <li>Develop features based on requirements.</li> <li>Deploy the application, apply CI/CD using bitbucket pipelines, docker, Nginx</li> </ul>
Technologies used	- Backend: Nestjs, Mongoose, Redis, Socket.io Frontend: Next.js, Redux, Cypress, Socket.io.

Continuum Cyber	(November 2021 - March 2022)
Continuum CybCi	(110 VCIIIUCI 2021 - Waicii 2022

Customer	Continuum
Description	A website vulnerability scanning service.
Team size	3
My position	Fullstack Web Developer
My responsibilities	- Develop features base on requirements Deploy the application, apply CI/CD using bitbucket pipelines, docker, Nginx
Technologies used	- Backend: Nodejs, PosgreSQL, Strapi, RabbitMQ, Socket.io. - Frontend: Next.js, Socket.io.

# IOT(Go-Virtual Event platform)

(May 2021 - July 2021)

Customer	Singex
Description	A platform to empower your community to discover connections, content, and recommendations to enable them to stay relevant and unlock a whole new universe of commerce, innovation, and growth.
Team size	7
My position	Fullstack Web Developer
My responsibilities	- Track events using Mixpanel Bug fixing.
Technologies used	- Backend: Nodejs, MongoDB, Redis, Restful API, Fastify, RabbitMQ, WebSocket. - Frontend: Next.js.

Epiq

(June 2021 - November 2021)

(valie 2021 1 to temper 1	
Customer	Bobabox
Description	A transcription service for court.
Team size	4
My position	Fullstack Web Developer
My responsibilities	- Develop features base on requirements.
Technologies used	- Backend: Nodejs, PosgreSQL, Redis, Restful API, Fastify, WebSocket Frontend: Next.js, Socket.io, Hls, Ffmpeg.

**Insurtech** (June 2020 - May 2021)

Customer	SaveMoney Corporation
Description	A digital insurance platform for Banks, Hospitals, and Telco companies based on strategic cooperation to share sustainable economic benefits.
Team size	15
My position	Fullstack Web Developer
My responsibilities	<ul> <li>- Implement new features in the system.</li> <li>- Associate with the Data Science team in order to solve requirements such as car pricing, verify device,</li> <li>- Work closely with QC, BA team, and product manager to determine problems, testing methods, and best practices.</li> <li>- Makes recommendations towards API Design and Database Design</li> <li>- Build APIs for payment integration with VNPay.</li> </ul>
Technologies used	- Backend: Nodejs, SequelizeJS, PostgreSQL, Redis, Restful API, Google Cloud API library, Microservice, GraphQL, Apollo GraphQL, Joi, Express, RabbitMQ - Frontend: UmiJS, Ant design, DvaJS, ReactJS, Redux

MAM (March 2021 - Now)

Customer	University Project
Description	MAM is social media for sharing recipes. Besides, the application also is a cooking assistant for chefs.
Team size	5
My position	Backend Web Developer

My responsibilities	<ul> <li>Analyze, design, develop and test software product features.</li> <li>Build backend codebase.</li> <li>Design architecture, database and API.</li> <li>Deploy the application to DigitalOcean using Docker.</li> <li>Apply CI/CD using Github Actions.</li> </ul>
Technologies used	<ul> <li>Backend: Nodejs, ExpressJS, Docker, Redis, PostgreSQL, Sequelize, Cloudinary, Socket.io server, ElasticSearch.</li> <li>Frontend: ReactJS, ReactNative, Redux Thunk, Redux Observable, Socket.io client, Firebase</li> </ul>

**Tdemy** (Oct 2020 - Dec 2020)

Customer	University Project
Description	Online academy platforms like Udemy, Coursera,
Team size	3
My position	Team Leader
My responsibilities	<ul> <li>Build frontend using Reactjs and participate in developing backend</li> <li>Build codebase.</li> <li>Participate in system design and code review.</li> <li>Responsible for people management.</li> <li>Bug Fixing.</li> </ul>
Technologies used	ReactJS, Redux Thunk, Ant Design, Expressjs, Postgres, Sequelize, Redis, Docker